Mom, I'm back.
Yang,
you are still doing homework so late.
The Olympiad mathematics contest is next month.
I need to do more exercises.
Yang, I'm sorry.
I worked late today.
I didn't cook for you.
It's okay.
Are you full?
Yes.
If you get hungry later,
I'll make you something.
Then let me work overtime with you.
Come on, Yang.
Let's work together.
Good luck, Mom.
Good luck.
Yang,
is your study
a bit tough lately?
I think you've lost
some weight.
I've been training in the basketball club.
I've got stronger.
Let me feel it.
You are indeed stronger.
It's late at night.
Don't drink too much coffee.
Okay, no more coffee.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Yang,
remember,
you have to go to bed
by 12:00.
Do you hear me?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, get to it.
A sequence of numbers
arranged in a certain order
like this
is called a sequence,
Each number in the sequence
is called an item.
If we categorize by the number of items,
there are finite sequences
and infinite sequences.
In memory of Zhou Yu in his heyday,
when he just married Xiao Qiao,
he was vigorous and valiant,
with feather fan and silk scarf,
he destroyed the enemy
with ease and laughter.
In my dreams, I return to my homeland...
What's wrong?
I'm so sleepy.
Poke me.
Lin Qingyuan,
go stand at the back.
Class,
today we're going to learn
the complex uses
of modal verbs.
Must indicates certainty.
When we're negating,
we use can't.
For uncertainty,
we use may,
should,
would,
and might.
So when using
modal verbs...
Ms. Wang,
this is the proposal for Reading Week.
Please take a look.
Okay.
Wait for me to finish reading it.
Zhou Yang,
are you feeling a bit tired lately?
Remember to balance work and rest.
I understand, ma'am.
I'll head back to the classroom now.
Go ahead.
Are you okay, Zhou Yang?
I'm fine.
Let's continue.
That's all
for today's class.
Goodbye, teacher.
Why don't you write down
your mistakes in your notebook?
Do you understand what this means?
Sorry, I don't know.
I've asked you
ten questions.
Don't you know any of them?
Yes.
Mr. Zhou, please.
Why don't you write our mistakes
on the blackboard?
Okay, I will.
Are you kidding me?
Yes.
Mr. Zhou, go on.
Okay.
Why don't we write down our mistakes
in the notebook?
This sentence means
we should write down our mistakes
in our mistake notebook.
Take a break first.
Your steps are unsteady.
Challenge.
Action.
Focus.
Suitable.
Can you not disturb me?
Okay.
Juice?
Sorry, please leave.
Good night.
Target.
Forward.
Replicated during interphase
during the interphase.
It consists of prophase, metaphase,
anaphase, and telophase.
Interphase...
Impressive.
What's up with Zhou Yang?
I don't know.
Something feels off.
Zhou Yang,
what's going on?
You don't look well.
It's nothing.
It won't affect my exam tomorrow.
Midterms are tomorrow.
Yibei Basketball Club.
Good luck on the exam.
Lin Qingyuan,
are you ready?
Yes.
Li Haoyu,
what about you?
Go.
Chinese.
Passed.
Math.
English.
Great, also passed.
And you?
Let's see yours.
I...
Chinese passed.
Math.
Passed.
History also passed.
Next is the final round.
Physics.
63.
Passed.
I've all passed. That's great.
Wait a moment, wait a moment, wait a moment.
You check my geography score for me.
Okay.
I really can't take it anymore.
The last digit.
It's six.
Tens place, tens place.
The tens digit, the tens digit is...
Six.
Lin Qingyuan,
your geography score is 66.
You passed.
It's really 66 points.
I passed all the subjects too.
Our rankings are safe.
We can continue to compete.
That's great.
Li Haoyu, catch the ball.
It's not easy.
Let's go.
Let's tell everyone
this good news.
Okay.
How did you two do?
Don't be like this.
Say something.
Gu Chenyang.
Are they going to cry?
Anyway,
you've tried your best.
So, actually...
You really believe we didn't pass?
Don't you know
who I am.
We all passed.
And our grades are all good.
Come on.
You scared me.
You two did well.
Your grades have improved a lot.
We can finally
prepare for the competition.
Yes.
Mr. Gu,
you deserve half the credit.
Yes.
Where's Mr. Zhou?
Why isn't he here
for such an important moment?
Right.
Zhou Yang
didn't do well this time.
Congrats.
You're the top student in the grade.
I...
I thought
I could do everything well.
I'm sorry to make a fool of myself.
It's not funny.
Don't you feel tired?
Let me be frank.
Is it worth it
for the basketball club?
Zhou Yang used to
never have such a big drop
in his academic performance.
If everyone can do better,
I think it's worth it.
After all, the Basketball Club
is not just about one person.
I just think
when will you
think more about yourself?
It's all because we are not competitive enough,
which has held Zhou Yang back.
Fortunately, I didn't fail this time.
or I'd be ashamed to see him.
Why aren't they talking?
I wonder if Fu Binyan
will scold him.
Should we go check?
No need.
Let's go back to training.
Aren't you worried about Zhou Yang?
Of course,
but right now,
the only thing we can do
is to prepare for the next game,
and not let his hard work go to waste.
We must win this game.
Let's go.
I'll get in the car right away.
Haven't you answered the phone yet?
What's going on?
The game will start
in ten minutes.
He's not someone who would be late.
Could something have happened to him?
Coach Su
Please designate the starting members
and sign.
Let the substitutes start.
Don't just stand there. Get warmed up.
Okay, coach.
Xu Anbo
Let Chi Jia continue to contact.
Notify me if anything happens.
You're awake.
Why are you here?
I took the bus
to the basketball hall this morning
and saw you faint.
The basketball hall, right.
Lie down.
What time is it now?
The game
is over.
What's the result?
54 to 72.
Yibei lost.
Because I didn't show up.
You fainted
from low blood sugar,
plus lack of sleep
and overexertion.
You'd
just hold us back
if you'd played.
I told you,
don't be so self-reliant.
Yeah,
I'm not strong enough.
I mean,
no one can carry everything
by themselves.
Not even superheroes.
Back in the basketball club,
the seniors
pushed everything onto you,
and you took it all.
You suddenly missed a game
was because of Auntie Xiao's
sudden appendicitis.
You had to rush to the hospital.
Later,
you had to take care of her
while preparing for the final exam.
But you,
didn't explain anything.
Even now,
they still hold a grudge against you.
I...
I just don't want to
cause any trouble for them.
What about your mom?
With all that's happened,
doesn't she know anything?
She's been busy with work.
I don't want to
add any more burden to her.
So,
your emergency contact is your dad?
Zhou Yang,
do you think this is being sensible?
This is being foolish, you know?
Zhou Yang,
sometimes,
you have to be willing to bother others.
Otherwise,
you'll make those who truly care about you
feel heartbroken.
After finishing the IV drip,
remember to eat something sweet.
Zhou Yang
Why are you here?
Why didn't you tell us?
Yeah.
You scared us.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
I just finished the infusion.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't make it to the competition.
Fu Binyan has told us.
You should have a good rest.
Don't think about anything else.
That's right.
You are more important than the match.
But next...
There is no but.
If anyone should say sorry,
it should be us.
We didn't do well,
but you are tired like this.
We should be the ones apologizing.
And we lost a race
we should've won.
It's my fault
for not keeping an eye
on your condition.
Alright,
stop it.
Are you holding
a review meeting here?
Lin Qingyuan's right.
The most important thing now
is to get well.
Haven't you eaten yet?
Name your order.
It's on me.
Stop it.
He's sick. He can't eat.
He can only eat porridge.
But
I really want a hamburger.
You're really taking advantage.
Give me my phone back.
I just need the payment password.
Payment for what? Seriously.
Stop arguing.
Don't you see where you are?
What did the doctor say?
When can he be discharged?
He should be able to leave tomorrow.
Don't worry.
I'll stay with you tonight.
No, I'll stay here.
My family doesn't care about me anyway.
You don't have to stay.
My mom will be here soon.
You've had a long day.
Go home early.
Well,
will your mom really come?
Why do you ask?
I'm afraid you
just don't want to bother us
and didn't tell your family the truth.
This time it's real.
That's good.
Take a good rest.
Thank you.
Bye.
We're leaving. Bye.
Don't look at me. Go back.
You must take a good rest.